turmswear.com 2019-07-05

# Privacy Policy – Turmswear

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy (" **Policy** ") details how BIGPHI Technologies Private Limited (" **BIGPHI** ", also identified by " **we** " or " **us** " or " **our** ") collects and uses your personal information when you use our web portal ( [www.turmswear.com](http://www.turmswear.com/)), which is referred to within this Policy as the " **turmswear.com** ", and any other service provided by us via any other medium related to BIGPHI (all these services collectively referred to as the " **Services** ").

We are publishing this Policy in line with our obligations under the Information Technology Act, 2000, so that users of our Services may be aware of our practices in relation to their privacy. By using or continuing to use the Services, you agree to our collection, storage, use and sharing of your information in accordance with this Policy, as may be amended from time to time by BIGPHI at its sole discretion. 

That stated, BIGPHI knows that you care about how the information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust in us to do that carefully and sensibly. We assure you that we are committed to respecting and upholding your privacy, and that our usage of your information is limited to activities which helps us improve the Services for you. If you have any questions at the end of this, do feel free to contact us at the coordinates listed below.

**
* Types of Information
**  
**
* Personal Information
**

Personal information, for the purposes of this Policy, refers to information that can specifically identify an individual user, visitor, customer (“ **User** ”) of ours, such as that User’s name, address, email address, payment data, telephone number etc. This would also include information about a User’s activities with regard to the usage of our Services, and demographic information, including nationality, date of birth, gender, geographic area, and preferences, whenever any such information is linked to the personal information that identifies a User.

**
* Aggregate Information
**

Aggregate Information, for the purposes of this Policy, refers to information about (i) a group of people defined by any characteristic such as nationality, age, gender, geographic area etc., or (ii) category of products, services, or users. Such Aggregate Information cannot be used to personally identify an individual, and from which individual identities are retracted. We may use and disclose Aggregate Information, and other non-personally identifiable information, for various purposes.

**
* Collection of Information
**

We collect both personal and aggregate information relating to the Users of our Services. In particular, Personal Information is made available to us in several different ways which are detailed below:

User Provided: We receive and store any information you directly provide to us, such as when you search, post, type, participate in an event, respond to a questionnaire, communicate with customer service on BIGPHI, or use a third-party seller’s platform that is associated with us. You can choose not to provide such information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features.

Examples of such User Provided information include: User names; User addresses and dispatch locations; User phone numbers; User login data; User designated financial information for payments; User associates to whom purchases have been dispatched (including addresses and phone numbers); search entries; information in User profiles; communications (e-mail or otherwise); User compilations like wish lists; inputs related to ratings and reviews; responses to personal notification services and order notifications.

Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information automatically whenever your device interacts with the turmswear.com. For instance, we use "cookies", which are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your device's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognise your browser; this enables us to offer personalized services to you and customize your overall experience. Further, we obtain certain types of information when your web browser accesses BIGPHI or advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of BIGPHI on other websites. We may also use browser data such as Flash cookies (also known as Flash Local Shared Objects), or similar data on certain parts of our website or mobile applications for fraud prevention and other purposes. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.

Examples of such Automatic Information includes: the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer or device to the Internet; device and connection information such as browser type and version; operating system and platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our turmswear.com (including date and time); cookie number; products viewed or searched for; any phone number used to call our customer service number.

Information provided by Third Parties: We may receive Personal information about you from third parties, such as social media services, commercially available sources and business partners. If you access / connect our Services through / to a social media service, you are authorizing BIGPHI to collect, store, use and retain all information associated with that social media service which is provided to us upon such access or connection.

Examples of information we receive from other sources include: user name; profile picture; email address; friends list; updated delivery and address information from couriers; account information; purchase information; page-view information etc.

E-mail Notifications: to help us make e-mails more useful and relevant, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from BIGPHI, if your device supports such capabilities. If you do not want to receive e-mails from us, please click on the unsubscribe link in the email.

**
* Usage of User Information
**We use the information we collect from Users in order to be able to effectively provide the Sevices, and to personalise and continually improve the experience offered to our Users. In general, such information is used for, but not limited to, the following purposes: **  
**

      1. provide the Services, which will include ; handling of orders; delivery of products; processing of payments; transactional communication; promotional communication; updation of User accounts / our records; enhancement of personalization features; recording of product reviews; resolution of fraud or abuses of our Services, facilitation of third party technical, logistical and other essential functions, etc.;
      2. enhance, improve, operate, deliver and maintain our Services, our programs, services, Web site, and other systems;
      3. offer you a customized experience, including personalization of the offerings on the turmswear.com;
      4. perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our or others’ products, services, or content;
      5. send you messages or notifications that may be of interest to you, such as notices of particular activity on the Services, newsletters, and promotional materials;
      6. respond to messages from you and to communicate with you by any medium possible about products or services from us or third parties that might be of specific use to you;
      7. prevent fraudulent use of our Services and other systems;
      8. prevent or take action against activities that are, or may be, in violation of our Terms of Service or applicable law;
      9. maintain a record of our dealings with you; and
      10. perform specific functions or services as otherwise described to you at the time of collection, pursuant to your consent.

We may use and share the Aggregate Information with third parties. This may be used to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our Service and on websites or applications of third parties, and to analyze and report on advertising you see. We also may share aggregated, non-personal information, or personal information in hashed, non-human readable form, with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the purpose of conducting general business analysis or other business purposes.

**
* Sharing Information with Third Parties:
**

Information about our customers is an important part of our business and we are not in the business of selling it to others. BIGPHI shares customer information only as described below:

Third Party Service Providers: We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as courier services, data analysis, marketing services, payment processing etc. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. Further, they must process the personal information in accordance with this Policy and as permitted by the applicable law.

Compliance with the Law: We may be required to share the personal information with government authorities and agencies for, inter alia, the purposes of verification of identity or for prevention, detection, investigation including cyber incidents, prosecution and punishment of offences. Further, we may release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property or safety of BIGPHI, our users or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies, organisations, government or regulatory authorities for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Business Transfers: All information, including Personal Information, collected and stored by us may be disclosed and otherwise transferred to an acquirer, or successor or assignee as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing, sale of company assets, or similar transaction, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership in which all such information is transferred to one or more third parties as one of our business assets. We assure you we will use our best efforts ot make sure that the transferee entity will follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Policy.

When you use the turmswear.com website, you may also be using the services of various third parties, such as Google, Facebook, MSD, YouTube Player. Your use of these third party services may be subject to the separate policies, terms of use, and fees of these third parties.

**
* Securing Information & Retention:
  
**We work to protect the security of your information during purchase of any product on turmswear.com. At the time of making an online payment, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software which encrypts information you input in addition to maintaining security of your information. We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. **  
**

We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards in connection with the collection, storage and disclosure of personal information (including sensitive personal information). Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose personal information to you.

If you choose a payment gateway to complete any transaction on Website or mobile applications then your credit card data may be stored in compliance with industry standards/ recommended data security standard for security of financial information such as the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS).

We take the protection of all information collected through the Services very seriously, and dedicate a significant amount of our resources to that. However it is impossible to guarantee the security of any virtual database or application, and consequently it is essential to exercise caution while using the turmswear.com, especially to protect against unauthorised access to your User account and password on the turmswear.com. Be sure to sign off when you finish using a shared computer.

**
* Use of Information and Duration:
**

BIGPHI will strive to protect the privacy and legal rights of users. Any and all Personal and Sensitive Information you provide to us will be retained by us and along with the rights to use the same, until you expressly direct us in writing to not use it further.

All Personal Information shall be retained till such time as required, even beyond for the purpose of rendering the Services or as required under applicable law, whichever is later, and Non-Personal Information may be retained indefinitely. If you delete your account on the turmswear.com website, we will retain your Personal Information for analytical purposes and recordkeeping integrity, as well as to prevent fraud, enforce our Terms of Use, take actions we deem necessary to protect the integrity of our Service or otherwise required / permitted by law. In addition, if certain information has already been provided to third parties as described in this Privacy Policy, retention of that information will be subject to those third parties' policies.

If you do not want us to use your Personal Information that to personalize your experience on our turmswear.com, please write to us at [support@turmswear.com](mailto:%20support@turmswear.com "support@turmswear.com").

**
* Associated Third Parties:
**

The Services may contain links to other websites, products or services that we do not own or operate, whether posted by us or a third party users of BIGPHI. If you choose to visit or use any third-party sites or products or services made available through a link on turmswear.com, please be aware that this Policy will not apply to your activities or any information you disclose while visiting or using those services. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any such third-party sites or any products or services on or through them.

**
* International Visitors:
**

If you are using our services from outside India, please be aware that your Personal Information may be sent to, stored and processed at our servers and data centers which are located in India. Hence by providing your personal information to us through your use of the Service, you agree to that transfer, storage, and processing in India. Also, we may transfer your data from India to other countries in connection with the operation of the Services. Note that each country has its own privacy and data security laws, which differ significantly from region to region, and hence those applicable to BIGPHI’s area of operation may not be as stringent as those in your home country

**
* Usage by Children
**

The Services and the usage of BIGPHI is available only to persons eligible to enter into legally binding contracts under Indian Contract Act, 1872, and this excludes minors (i.e. persons under the age of 18). If you are a minor, you shall not register as a User of the Services and shall not transact on or use BIGPHI, unless such transaction is made on your behalf by your legal guardian on our platform. 

**
* Notices and Revisions:
**

Our business changes constantly and our Privacy Notice and the Terms of Use will change also. Accordingly, we will be updating this Policy from time to time, and when such changes are made we shall indicate the date of updation on the top of this document. Any such changes will be applicable to you provided your continued usage of the Services beyond the date of updation. While we may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, we recommend that you check this Policy from time to time to ensure that you are fully informed of any changes that might affect you.

Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.

Please contact us for further queries: [support@turmswear.com](mailto:%20support@turmswear.com "support@turmswear.com")

This Policy should be at all times read along with the Terms of Use of the Website.
